MANISHA PRIYA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Result Oriented person having experience of over 7 + years in multiple domain like E-commerce Account Management of Men's and Women's Apparel, Shoes and other GL and Electronic Distributor Industry, along with Business Development in Business Media.

EXPERIENCE

Assistant Account Management Specialist, 09/2019 - Current Amazon Development Centre - Bangalore

- Managing 25 key account whose monthly range from 2 Lacs-20 Lacs and above on Amazon.in and enabling them to grow faster on platform to increase their share in Apparel category.
- Identifying valuable sellers and work on growth backward strategy while understanding the gap to business growth so as to enabling Brand/ Sellers on FBA model, Amazon Advertisement, Catalogue improvement and another Amazon program.
- Planning and Preparing Business Plan of year for each high contributing GMS Brand through meeting.
- Work closely with Leadership on planning and business strategy for Apparel, completing in-depth analysis into customer trends.
- Driving individual projects on Advertisement, Regionalization of Inventory metrics and Seller Suspension across the Department and GL to enable Account Manager so that they will nudge sellers with right training.

Sales Associate- Amazon Advertising (Sept 2019- May 2020)

- Working on Brand/Seller Advertisement Campaign Creation and Advertisement.
- Analyze campaign performance against key metrics to identify, recommend, and implement optimizations to increase efficiency, drive high renewal rate and meet clients' KPIs
- Serve as a source of market intelligence for other areas of the Advertising team (e.g., product development, product marketing, pricing) and assist in the development of best practices and operational efficiencies

Account Development Representative, 05/2017 - 08/2019 Element14 India Private Limited

- Account Management and Cold Calling
- Maximize sales to customers through effective identification of cross/up selling and campaign opportunities while working on quotation for low margin approval.
- Delivery customer satisfaction



CONTACT

Address: Bangalore, 560062

Phone: 8105952341

Email: 5manisha2priya@gmail.com

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Strategic Account Management
- Amazon Advertisement
- Brand Management and Development
- Analytical Skill
- Inventory Management
- Market and Competitive Analysis
- Project Management
- Team Management
- Telesales
- Business Development
- Lead Generation

Lead Generation Executive, 01/2017 - 04/2017 Barefoot Power India

- Identifying new leads and connect with International organization which help to promote solar home lighting
- Researching organization and individual online to identify new leads and potential markets
- Connecting with decision makers of shortlisted organizations through email and follow up over a call
- Send the proposal and share the concept of solar energy
- Close the proposal.

Business Development Manager, 12/2015 - 01/2017 Insights Success Media and Technology Private Limited

- Researching organization and individuals online to identify new leads and potential new markets
- Researching the needs of other companies and learning who makes decision about purchasing
- Contacting potential clients via e-mail or phone to establish rapport and set up closures
- Negotiating and renegotiating by phone and email
- Development sales goals for team and ensuring they met
- Training personal and helping team members to develop their skills.

EDUCATION

MBA, Marketing, 2015, S.M.U - Patna

B.COM, 2012, Magadh Mahila College (Patna University - Patna

12th, 2009, D.A.V Public School - Patna

10th, 2007, St. Joseph's High School - Patna

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

- Promoted in Amazon Development Centre (Prione Business) from Account Management Associate to Assistant Account Management Specialist in May 2022 and received Multiple RNR awards
- Promoted as Business Development Manager in Insight Success